Machine Learning and Computer Vision Researcher

Tehran, Poonak +98 937 862 9071 homoradi@ut.ac.ir homayouneemoradi



## WHO AM I?

Experienced Head of R&D with a demonstrated history of working in Machine Learning and Computer Vision fields. Skilled AI Researcher with a Master of Science from Tehran Univer-

Computer Vision Deep Learning Machine Learning Data Analysis Neuroscience Sci-kit Robotics

Pytorch Opencv MongoDB Pandas Flask













## **EXPERIENCE**

2019 - Presnet part time

**Computer Vision Engineer** 

Knowledge Extraction and Intention Recognition Using Cutting Edge AI Technologies.

2018 - 2021 part time

**Head of Computer Vision Team** 

Control and AI Lab - IUST

Multi-Agent and Autonomous Vehicles 3D Perception, Road Scene Understanding and Analysis of Surveillance Videos.

2016 - 2018 Co-Founder

The First Online 3D Printing Service and Social Marketplace Based in Tehran. We Made an Online

Platform That Provides 3D Printing Services by Connecting Customers and Vendors.

2015 - 2016 **Control Engineer**  CETEC

**SUSLIB** 

### **PROJECTS**

Smart Smile Desing based-on Computer Vision Techniques (ongoing) Recommender System based-on Hybrid Approach for Torob.com - Datadays2021 (3rd rank in first phase - ongoing)

2021 2020 2019

COVID-19 Tweets Analysis Persian OCR

Table Structure Recognition Face Spoofing Detection

Music Metadata and Text Analysis Scene Multi-Label Classification

tsetms+Sahamyab Data Analysis Face Detection and Recognition **Human Action Recognition** Image Retrieval

Fusion-based 3D Object Analysis Aerial Image Segmentation Supermarket Product Counter Multiple Object Tracking

# **EDUCATION**

2019 - Presnet Master of Science - MS, Artificial Intelligence GPA:19.23 **Tehran University** 

Advisor: Prof. Behzad Moshiri and Dr. Mehdi Tale Masoole

Thesis: Human-Robot Interaction Using Soft/Hard Information Fusion, Case Study: NAO Robot Research Assistant at NBIC, Supervised by Dr. MohammadReza A. Dehagani, Human Action Classification Using EEG Signal Processing

Teaching Assistant for Big Data, Dr. Masoud Asadpour - Spring 2021

2016 - 2019 Master of Business Administration - MBA, Finance

Kharazmi University

2012 - 2016 **Bachelor's Degree, Control Engineering** 

Iran University of Science and Technology (IUST)

Advisor: Prof. Aliakbar Jalali

Thesis: IoT for Smart Cities: Use Cases and Implementation Strategies

Activities: Teaching Assistant for Signal and Systems, Prof. Aliakbar Jalali - Fall 2019